Card.create(question: "Alabama", answer: "Montgomery")
Card.create(question: "Alaska", answer: "Juneau")
Card.create(question: "Arizona", answer: "Phoenix")
Card.create(question: "Arkansas", answer: "Little Rock")
Card.create(question: "California", answer: "Sacramento")
Card.create(question: "Colorado", answer: "Denver")
Card.create(question: "Connecticut", answer: "Hartford")
Card.create(question: "Delaware", answer: "Dover")
Card.create(question: "Florida", answer: "Tallahassee")
Card.create(question: "Georgia", answer: "Atlanta")
Card.create(question: "Hawaii", answer: "Honolulu")
Card.create(question: "Idaho", answer: "Boise")
Card.create(question: "Illinois", answer: "Springfield")
Card.create(question: "Indiana", answer: "Indianapolis")
Card.create(question: "Iowa", answer: "Des Moines")
Card.create(question: "Kansas", answer: "Topeka")
Card.create(question: "Kentucky", answer: "Frankfort")
Card.create(question: "Louisiana", answer: "Baton Rouge") 
Card.create(question: "Maine", answer: "Augusta")
Card.create(question: "Maryland", answer: "Annapolis")
Card.create(question: "Massachusetts", answer: "Boston")
Card.create(question: "Michigan", answer: "Lansing")
Card.create(question: "Minnesota", answer: "Saint Paul") 
Card.create(question: "Mississippi", answer: "Jackson")
Card.create(question: "Missouri", answer: "Jefferson City") 
Card.create(question: "Montana", answer: "Helena")
Card.create(question: "Nebraska", answer: "Lincoln")
Card.create(question: "Nevada", answer: "Carson City") 
Card.create(question: "New Hampshire", answer: "Concord") 
Card.create(question: "New Jersey", answer: "Trenton")
Card.create(question: "New Mexico", answer: "Santa Fe")
Card.create(question: "New York", answer: "Albany")
Card.create(question: "North Carolina", answer: "Raleigh")
Card.create(question: "North Dakota", answer: "Bismarck")
Card.create(question: "Ohio", answer: "Columbus")
Card.create(question: "Oklahoma", answer: "Oklahoma City") 
Card.create(question: "Oregon", answer: "Salem")
Card.create(question: "Pennsylvania", answer: "Harrisburg")
Card.create(question: "Rhode Island", answer: "Providence")  
Card.create(question: "South Carolina", answer: "Columbia")
Card.create(question: "South Dakota", answer: "Pierre")  
Card.create(question: "Tennessee", answer: "Nashville")
Card.create(question: "Texas", answer: "Austin")
Card.create(question: "Utah", answer: "Salt Lake City") 
Card.create(question: "Vermont", answer: "Montpelier")
Card.create(question: "Virginia", answer: "Richmond")
Card.create(question: "Washington", answer: "Olympia")
Card.create(question: "West Virginia", answer: "Charleston") 
Card.create(question: "Wisconsin", answer: "Madison")
Card.create(question: "Wyoming", answer: "Cheyenne")

Deck.create(name: 'State Capitols')
